coverme guaranteed issue life insurance
from manual Life Financial no one wants
to leave their family with costly
funeral expenses or other debts and
thanks to coverme guaranteed issue life
insurance you don't have to because if
you're between 40 and 75 your acceptance
is guaranteed that's right you cannot be
turned down for coverage regardless of
your health or medical history and there
is no medical exam and no health
questions when you apply plus your
premiums which can start as low as $25 a
month will never increase and your
coverage will never decrease you will be
insured for life and your coverage can
never be canceled as long as your
premiums are paid and in the case of
accidental death your beneficiary may
receive a benefit equal to five times
your coverage Plus cover me guaranteed
issue life comes with a 30-day money
back guarantee remember coverme
guaranteed issue life is Affordable and
your acceptance is guaranteed so don't
delay for your free no obligation
brochure call or visit coverme.com now